[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie features a character with a face painted white and with nails all over his head.", "correct_answer": "Hellraiser", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabin Fever", "Spookies", "Rawhead Rex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the Great Fire of London occur?", "correct_answer": "1666", "incorrect_answers": ["1866", "1566", "1766"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In early 2009, Scarlett Johansson was announced as the face of the new make-up collection by which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Dolce  Gabbana", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis Vuitton", "Calvin Klein", "L\u2019Oreal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We watch TV thanks to which of these processes forming light?", "correct_answer": "Cathodoluminescence", "incorrect_answers": ["Fiboluuminescence", "Bioluminescence", "Sololuminescence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a box turtle is taken out of the wild, it can spend years and sometimes its entire life looking for its home.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Earthquakes that occur at the boundaries of tectonic plates are called interplate. The less frequent type of earthquakes, called this, occur in the interior of the lithospheric plates.", "correct_answer": "Intraplate", "incorrect_answers": ["Innerplate", "Non-interplate", "Ultraplate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1965 movie, Thunderball, how many atomic bombs are stolen from the jet fighter that disappears from radar?", "correct_answer": "Two", "incorrect_answers": ["One", "None", "Three"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the brown aura associated with in parapsychology?", "correct_answer": "Greed", "incorrect_answers": ["Spite", "Disease", "Serenity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the first manned rocket flights into space, pencils, not pens, were given to the cosmonauts and astronauts. Why?", "correct_answer": "Pencils can write in zero gravity.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were less dangerous because they contained no metal.", "They were less affected by lower amounts of oxygen.", "Pencils are lighter than pens."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two cats are the main characters in the Lillian Jackson Braun series?", "correct_answer": "Koko and Yumyum", "incorrect_answers": ["Yin and Yang", "Kitty Jones and Kat  Smith", "Rin and Tintin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of their body do Tasmanian devils store body fat?", "correct_answer": "Tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Abdomen", "Neck", "Back"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The TriRhena Euroregion is spans these three countries crossed by the Rhine River.", "correct_answer": "France, Germany and Switzerland", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium, Germany and Luxembourg", "Austria, Germany and Switzerland", "France, Germany and Holland"]}]